{
    "subject": "resource/The_Cable_Guy",
    "predicate": "ontology/Work/runtime",
    "object": "96.0",
    "human_readable": "The Cable Guy has a runtime of 96.0.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6092591285705566,
            "question": "What is the runtime of the movie 'The Cable Guy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5881350636482239,
            "question": "Does the runtime of 'The Cable Guy' seem appropriate for its genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5749367475509644,
            "question": "Would you expect 'The Cable Guy' to be a fast-paced movie based on its runtime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4544718265533447,
            "question": "Would a shorter runtime make 'The Cable Guy' more appealing to some viewers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42176708579063416,
            "question": "How does the runtime of 'The Cable Guy' compare to other movies you've seen recently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40895867347717285,
            "question": "Compare the runtime of 'The Cable Guy' to an average movie length."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2661904990673065,
            "question": "Is 'The Cable Guy' a short film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23882490396499634,
            "question": "Approximately how much time would it take to watch 'The Cable Guy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21700482070446014,
            "question": "If you had an hour and a half free, could you watch 'The Cable Guy' in full?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11972057074308395,
            "question": "How long is the movie 'The Cable Guy' in minutes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Cable Guy has a runtime of 96.0.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7188_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you had an hour and a half free, could you watch 'The Cable Guy' in full?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7188_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Approximately how much time would it take to watch 'The Cable Guy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7188_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Cable Guy' a short film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7188_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7188_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is about evaluating whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"The Cable Guy has a runtime of 96.0.\".\n\nGiven the context information, here's the evaluation:\n\n* Each episode of The Cable Guy is 96 minutes long (document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7188/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt)\n* The film \u2018The Cable Guy\u2019 has a running time of 96 minutes (document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7188/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt)\n\nSince both documents confirm the runtime of The Cable Guy as 96 minutes, which is equivalent to 96.0 in decimal form, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}